

Wiktoria Zasada

UX/UI Designer

Research-Driven | Humanist | International Experience

About me

I'm a creative 23 year old UX/UI Designer with international experience, passionate about crafting intuitive and engaging interfaces based on user research and analysis. My goal is to design seamless, user-friendly experiences that connect people with technology.

Education

Higher Education

CSG Bogerman Balk/Sneek, Netherlands 2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Science-Communication & Multimedia Design

NHL Stenden University of Applied Sciences, Leeuwarden, Netherlands 2020 - 2024

Contact

- wiktoria.s.zasada@gmail.com
- **%** +49 155 101 137 26
- Nordkirchen, Germany

Portfolio

https://wiktoriazasada.com

Languages

Polish Native

Dutch Fluent

English Fluent

German Intermediate

Experience

Content Designer

E-learning Platform For Kids, Klare Koek, Netherlands 2022 - 2024

Internship

Web-design, Klare Koek, Netherlands 2023 - 2023

UX Researcher

Web-design, Bowinn, Netherlands 2022 - 2023

UX/UI Designer

E-learning Web-App for iOS, Ottiya, South Korea 2022 - 2022

Skills

UX & UI Design

- Conducting user research, mapping user flows and user journeys to inform design decisions
- Creating UI Design Systems aligned with brand guidelines
- Wireframing and prototyping in both low- and highfidelity
- Designing visually engaging mockups in compliance with WCAG 2.1 accessibility standards

Soft skills

Teamwork, Great communication, Time Management, Growth Mindset, **Thinking out of the box**

Tools

Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Affinity Designer, Affinity Publisher, Affinity Photo, Slack, Miro, Microsoft Office, Notion



Wiktoria Zasada

UX/UI Designerin

Research-Driven | Humanistisch | Internationale Erfahrung

Über mich

Ich bin eine kreative 23-jährige UX/UI-Designerin mit internationaler Erfahrung, leidenschaftlich darin, intuitive und ansprechende Benutzeroberflächen auf Grundlage von Nutzerforschung und -analyse zu gestalten. Mein Ziel ist es, nahtlose und benutzerfreundliche Erlebnisse zu entwerfen, die Menschen mit Technologie verbinden.

Ausbildung

Gymnasium

CSG Bogerman Balk/Sneek, Niederlande 2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Science-Communication & Multimedia Design

NHL Stenden University of Applied Sciences, Leeuwarden, Niederlande 2020 - 2024

Kontakt

- wiktoria.s.zasada@gmail.com
- **%** +49 155 101 137 26
- Nordkirchen, Deutschland

Portfolio

https://wiktoriazasada.com

Sprachen

Polnish Muttersprache

Niederlandisch Fließend English Fließend

Deutsch Fortgeschritten

Erfahrung

Content Designer

E-learning Platform For Kids, Klare Koek, Niederlande 2022 - 2024

Praktikum

Web-design, Klare Koek, Niederlande 2023 - 2023

UX Researcher

Web-design, Bowinn, Niederlande 2022 - 2023

UX/UI Designer

E-learning Web-App für iOS, Ottiya, Südkorea 2022 - 2022

Skills

UX & UI Design

- Durchführung von User Research sowie Erstellung von User Flows und User Journeys zur Unterstützung von Designentscheidungen
- Erstellung von UI-Designsystemen im Einklang mit den Markenrichtlinien
- Erstellung von Wireframes und Prototypen in Lowund High-Fidelity
- Gestaltung visuell ansprechender Mockups unter Einhaltung der WCAG 2.1-Barrierefreiheitsstandards

Soft skills

Teamwork, Great communication, Time Management, Growth Mindset, **Thinking out of the box**

Tools

Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Affinity Designer, Affinity Publisher, Affinity Photo, Slack, Miro, Microsoft Office, Notion